□+(1)647-973-6640 | ■ andrewsivabalan@gmail.com | □ Cradle0 | □ andrew-sivabalan

Summary_

I am a Math and Computer Science graduate with additive knowledge from my previous Accounting experiences. I have tutored in Math, done basic accounting and fast food retail work. My adeptness developed from the intense problem solving from my undergraduate has prepared me for many challenging tasks.

Skills

Programming Python, C

Machine Learning Related Frameworks pytorch, sci-kit, jupyter, numpy

Projects

MNIST Label Predictor

· Labeled handwritten digits with classifying techniques such as kNN, logistic regression, Naive Bayes and Gaussian Discriminant.

Internet of Things Gateway Controller and Signal

Code Dec 2019

Oct 2021

· Created functions to handle messaging and communication between a gateway and controller in an IoT environment.

Parallel Make Program

Nov 2019

• Created a Parallel Make program that parse Makefiles that evaluates and execute with the option of doing so in parallel.

Work Experience _____

Klue

Vancouver, British Columbia

(Remote) Oct 2022 - Mar 2023

DATA ANALYST INTERN

- Developed an automated script reconciles data gathered to see if all data has been collected resulting in reducing manual work by over 50%, from 2 weeks+ for a customer down to 1 week
- · Demonstrated strong programming, problem-solving and adaptability by building the automation script from scratch independently which positively impacted Klue by increasing efficiency

Pizzaiolo Toronto, Ontario

CASHIER AND GENERAL BOOKKEEPER

Dec. 2019 - Apr. 2021

- Communicated and served over 50 customers a day at the cashier by preparing their order and managing the line, ensuring a quick and pleasant
- · Accounted for general expenses and revenue through Excel spreadsheets to keep track of expenditure and profit and to ensure that future expenditures where for increasing profits and were necessary to the functioning of the business.

Education

Brock University

University of Toronto

Toronto, Canada

HONOURS BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Sept. 2015 - Apr. 2022

· Graduated with Distinction - 3.23 cGPA

St. Catherines, Canada

HONOURS BACHELOR OF ACCOUNTING

Sept. 2013 - Dec. 2014